[
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "I ... tall",
        "answer" : "am"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "You ... 10 years old",
        "answer" : "are"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "He ... a little dog",
        "answer" : "has"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "Carla and I ... in the same class",
        "answer" : "are"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "They ... a good job",
        "answer" : "have"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "Sophie ... American",
        "answer" : "is"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "John and Peter ... twin brothers",
        "answer" : "are"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "She ... a big computer",
        "answer" : "has"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "You ... beautiful",
        "answer" : "are"
    },
    {
        "category": "verb",
        "question" : "James and you ... a black dog",
        "answer" : "have"
    }
]